♪ “Stampede”
by Genesis Owusu ♪
Once you've been to the moon...
♪
[WHOOSHING]
...where do you go next?
♪
Back to work.
[CLICKING]
♪
You start with the chip.
You engineer a new CPU core.
You engineer a new GPU core.
You add a second Neural Engine.
Now you've just doubled
the compute power,
pushed graphics
up to 40 per cent faster,
unlocked Siri AI
and built the fastest chip
ever put in an iPhone.
♪
But there's a catch:
More power creates more heat.
So you give the vapour chamber
three times more surface area,
because a bigger vapour chamber
cools the chip.
A cooler chip creates
a more efficient chip.
A more efficient chip
uses less battery.
♪
A battery that works less
lasts longer.
♪
The ultimate battery life.
[CLICK]
Next, you strengthen it...
[THUD]
[HISSING]
...and test it...
♪
...for wherever you need
to take it.
Then you ask, "What's next
for the camera system?"
You want to improve
low-light photography
and depth of field,
so you design
and prototype
until you’ve just invented
the first variable aperture
on an iPhone.
♪
A variable aperture
that automatically adjusts
in any lighting condition,
and improves sharpness
throughout a scene.
[CAMERA SHUTTER]
You also want
to give photographers
more creative control.
So you add pro controls,
allowing them to quickly
set aperture, shutter speed
and the colour balance
of an image.
[WAVES LAPPING]
And because you have
the most powerful chip
ever put in an iPhone...
♪
...you can push the camera
even further.
[CAMERA SHUTTERS]
You can shoot time-lapse in 4K
with high dynamic range.
[WIND RUSHING]
You can apply Cinematic mode
to a regular video,
even after you've shot it.
♪
You can customise
texture and grain
with Photographic Styles.
[CAMERA SHUTTERS]
[WHIRRING]
Now you’ve just created
a camera system so intelligent
and so capable that
photographers and filmmakers
can reach new levels
of creativity.
♪
[WAVES CRASHING]
[MECHANICAL WHIRRING]
♪
A chip built for AI
that runs faster than ever.
A battery that lasts
longer than ever.
The most intelligent
pro camera system ever.
This is what happens
when you go to the moon,
come back and ask,
“What’s next?”
♪